(Howard(on phone):)Okay.
(Penny:)Now imagine
you're holding that pen.
(Howard(on phone):)Okay.
(Penny:)Now open your hand
and let it go.
(Sheldon:)But I just got this pen.
(Sheldon:)It's got my initials on it
and everything.
(Leonard:)Look.
(Penny:)Sheldon, this isn't
that hard.
(Sheldon:)I may have a better way
that you can teach me.
(Penny:)How?
(Sheldon:)What if I told you
that over the past few months
(Sheldon:)Amy has secretly been giving you
little puzzles
(Sheldon:)to test your intelligence
against chimpanzees in her lab?
(Penny:)What? She didn't
give me any puzzles.
(Sheldon:)Are you sure?
(Amy(in flashback):)Boy, I just can't seem to get
these scissors back together.
(Amy(in flashback):)Can you do it?